Hiya Barbie
Hi Ken!
Do you want to go for a ride?
Sure Ken
Jump in
I'm a Barbie girl‚ in a Barbie world
Life in plastic‚ it's fantastic
You can brush my hair‚ undress me everywhere
Imagination‚ life is your creation
Come on Barbie‚ let′s go party!
I'm a Barbie girl‚ in a Barbie world
Life in plastic‚ it's fantastic
You can brush my hair‚ undress me everywhere
Imagination‚ life is your creation
I'm a blond bimbo girl, in a fantasy world
Dress me up‚ make it tight‚ I'm your dolly
You're my doll‚ rock′n′roll‚ feel the glamour in pink
Kiss me here‚ touch me there‚ hanky panky
You can touch
you can play
if you say I'm always yours
I'm a Barbie girl‚ in a Barbie world
Life in plastic‚ it's fantastic
You can brush my hair‚ undress me everywhere
Imagination‚ life is your creation
Come on Barbie‚ let′s go party!
Make me walk‚ make me talk‚ do whatever you please
I can act like a star‚ I can beg on my knees
Come jump in‚ bimbo friend‚ let us do it again
Hit the town‚ fool around‚ let′s go party
You can touch
you can play
If you say I'm always yours
You can touch
you can play
If you say I'm always yours
Come on Barbie‚ let′s go party!
I'm a Barbie girl‚ in a Barbie world
Life in plastic‚ it's fantastic
You can brush my hair‚ undress me everywhere
Imagination‚ life is your creation
I'm a Barbie girl‚ in a Barbie world
Life in plastic‚ it's fantastic
You can brush my hair‚ undress me everywhere
Imagination‚ life is your creation
Come on Barbie‚ let′s go party!
Oh‚ I'm having so much fun!
Well Barbie‚ we're just getting started
Oh‚ I love you Ken