I will run I will climb I will soar
I'm undefeated
Jumping out of my skin pull the chord
Yeah I believe it
The past is everything we were don't make us who we are
So I'll dream until I make it real and all I see is stars
It's not until you fall that you fly
When your dreams come alive you're unstoppable
Take a shot chase the sun find the beautiful
We will glow in the dark turning dust to gold
And we'll dream it possible
Possible
We'll dream it possible
I will chase I will reach I will fly
Until I'm breaking until I'm breaking
Out of my cage like a bird in the night
I know I'm changing I know I'm changing
In into something big better than before
And if it takes takes a thousand lives
Then it's worth fighting for
It's not until you fall that you fly
When your dreams come alive you're unstoppable
Take a shot chase the sun find the beautiful
We will glow in the dark turning dust to gold
And we'll dream it possible
it possible
From the bottom to the top
We're sparking wild fires
Never quit and never stop
The rest of our lives
From the bottom to the top
We're sparking wild fires
Never quit and never stop
It's not until you fall that you fly
When your dreams come alive you're unstoppable
Take a shot chase the sun find the beautiful
We will glow in the dark turning dust to gold
And we'll dream it possible
Possible
We'll dream it possible